Get lost in translation.
Language Lessons is a drama, comedy film directed by Natalie Morales.
For his 45th birthday, wealthy Californian Adam receives a surprise gift from his choreographer partner: 100 weekly
Spanish lessons with Cariño, a vivacious expat who teaches virtually from her home in Costa Rica.
Adam's unconvinced at first; a self-described “creature-of-habit”, he’s unsure about where
or how this new element will fit into his carefully-structured routine.
Adam, played by Mark Duplass.
Cariño, played by Natalie Morales.
Will, played by Desean Terry.
Cariño's Cousin (voice), played by Christine Quesada.
Language Lessons is a 2021 American screenlife drama film directed by Natalie Morales
(in her directorial debut) and written by Morales and Mark Duplass.
The film stars Morales, Duplass and Desean Terry.
The film follows the unexpected friendship that develops between Adam, a man whose
husband surprises him with online Spanish lessons, and his teacher, Cariño.
The film had its worldwide premiere at the 71st Berlin
International Film Festival on March 1, 2021.
It was released on September 10, 2021, by Shout!
The film explores themes of language course,
platonic love, webcam, teacher, grief.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.